Guide to the Consumer Reports. Audiovisual materials, 1940-2011 and undated RL.11802
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Advocacy and Consumer Education, 1940-2011; undated; 1
  - Policy Advocacy, 1959-2005; undated; 6
    - Conference on Ending Poverty, morning session, 1986 (Box 23, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1242)
    - Conference on Ending Poverty, reel 1, 1986 (Box 23, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-218)
    - Conference on Ending Poverty, reel 2, 1986 (Box 23, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-219)
    - Conference on Ending Poverty, reel 3, 1986 (Box 23, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-220)
    - Conference on Ending Poverty, reel 4, 1986 (Box 23, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-221)
    - Conference on Ending Poverty, reel 5, 1986 (Box 23, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-222)
    - Conference on Ending Poverty, reel 6, 1986 (Box 23, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-223)
    - Conference on Ending Poverty, reel 7, 1986 (Box 23, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-224)
    - Conference on Ending Poverty, video 1, 1986 (Box 23, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-242)
      9:30 AM middle class part 2
    - Conference on Ending Poverty, video 2, 1986 (Box 23, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-243)
      10:30 welfare (Rhoda's remarks part 1
    - Conference on Ending Poverty, video 3, 1986 (Box 23, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-244)
    - Conference on Ending Poverty, video 4, 1986 (Box 23, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-245)
    - Conference on Ending Poverty, video 5, 1986 (Box 23, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-246)
      3:30 PM final session
    - Conference on Ending Poverty, video 6, 1986 (Box 23, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-247)
    - Conference on Ending Poverty: Issues for the Middle Class Tape 2, 1986 Nov. 20-21 (Box 35, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-009)
    - Conference on Ending Poverty: Issues for the Middle Class Tape 3, 1986 Nov. 20-21 (Box 35, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-008)
    - Conference on Ending Poverty--Master Tape 01 Poverty Conference Columbia Room, 1986 Nov. 20 (Box 35, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-016)
    - Conference on Ending Poverty--Master Tape 02 Conference on Ending Poverty, 1986 Nov. 21 (Box 35, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-017)
    - Conference on Ending Poverty--Master Tape 03 Poverty Conference, 1986 Nov. 21 (Box 35, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-015)
    - Conference on Ending Poverty--Master Tape 04 Luncheon Address, 1986 Nov. 21 (Box 35, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-013)
    - Conference on Ending Poverty--Master Tape 05 Food & Hunger, 1986 Nov. 21 (Box 35, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-011)
    - Conference on Ending Poverty--Master Tape 06 Health Care & Illness, 1986 Nov. 21 (Box 35, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-012)
    - Conference on Ending Poverty--Master Tape 07 Poverty Conference Dinner Address, 1986 Nov. 21 (Box 35, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-010)
    - Conference on Ending Poverty--Master Tape 09 Poverty Conference What's Happening to the Middle Class, 1986 Nov. 21 (Box 35, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-029)
    - Conference on Ending Poverty--Master Tape 10 What do we do About Welfare, 1986 Nov. 21 (Box 35, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-031)
    - Conference on Ending Poverty--Master Tape 11 Lunch: Keynote Address, 1986 Nov. 21 (Box 35, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-032)
    - Conference on Ending Poverty--Master Tape 12 Safety Net Debate, 1986 Nov. 21 (Box 35, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-033)
    - Conference on Ending Poverty--Master Tape 13 Food Programs, 1986 Nov. 21 (Box 35, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-027)
    - Conference on Ending Poverty--Master Tape 14 Housing Day 2, 1986 Nov. 21 (Box 35, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-028)
    - Conference on Ending Poverty--Master Tape 15 Health Care Workshop, 1986 Nov. 21 (Box 35, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-038)
    - Conference on Ending Poverty--Master Tape 16 SSI Panel, 1986 Nov. 21 (Box 35, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-037)
    - Conference on Ending Poverty--Master Tape 17 The Future, 1986 Nov. 21 (Box 35, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-036)
    - Consumer Product Safety Commission Nomination, 2001 July 24 (Box 107, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0661)
    - Consumer Products Manila Letters (microfilm), 1969 (Box 138, Film-reel RL11802-F16-210)
      U.S. government, multiple addresses A-Z
    - Consumer Products Manila Letters (microfilm), 1970-1971 (Box 138, Film-reel RL11802-F16-211)
    - Consumer Products Manila Letters (microfilm), 1971 (Box 138, Film-reel RL11802-F16-212)
    - Consumer Union: Sample Testimony, 2003 Feb. 05 (Box 101, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-271)
    - Deregulation VO/SOT/B-Roll, 2002 May 30 (Box 107, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-156)
    - Deregulation VO/SOT/B-Roll, 2002 May 30 (Box 107, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-158)
    - Deregulation VO/SOT/B-Roll, 2002 May 30 (Box 107, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-159)
    - Deregulation VO/SOT/B-Roll, 2002 May 30 (Box 107, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-160)
    - Deregulation VO/SOT/B-Roll, 2002 May 30 (Box 107, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-162)
    - Deregulation VO/SOT/B-Roll, 2002 May 30 (Box 107, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-170)
    - District Attorney Phone Fraud Roof, 1993 Jan. 14 (Box 66, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0117)
    - Faces of Foreclosure Consumer Union, Undated (Box 1, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-002)
    - Faces of Foreclosure Consumer Union, Undated (Box 61, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-040)
    - G.W. Bush Record in Texas, 2000 Nov. 03 (Box 106, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1003)
    - Horace Kallen Lecture at New School #186a, 1973 Oct. 10 (Box 115, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-117)
    - Horace Kallen Lecture at New School #186b, 1973 Oct. 03 (Box 115, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-118)
    - Horace Kallen Lecture at New School #186c, 1973 Oct. 10 (Box 115, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-119)
    - Houghton Mifflin Company Protecting Consumers' Right to Accurate Information: Consumers Union, 2005 Dec. 02 (Box 1, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0001)
    - In Debt We Trust America Before the Bubble Bursts, Undated (Box 61, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-034)
    - Jim Guest Change Makers Struggle for Consumer Rights, Undated (Box 70, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-346)
    - Job Corps Consumer Education FS29, Ads, approximately 1964 (Box 138, Film-reel RL11802-F35-019)
    - Job Corps Consumer Education FS30, Labels, approximately 1964 (Box 138, Film-reel RL11802-F35-020)
    - Joint Council on Economic Education: The U.S. Economy in Action series FS16, 1963 (Box 138, Film-reel RL11802-F35-016)
      The Role of Consumers Part 1
    - Joint Council on Economic Education: The U.S. Economy in Action series FS16, 1963 (Box 138, Film-reel RL11802-F35-017)
      The Role of Consumers Part 2
    - Joint Council on Economic Education: The U.S. Economy in Action series FS16, 1963 (Box 138, Film-reel RL11802-F35-018)
      The Role of Consumers Part 3
    - Kilmer Job Corps, 1966 Feb. 28 (Box 75, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-116)
    - M. Silbergeld Regulatory reform, 1995 Apr. 03 (Box 68, Audio-cassette RL11802-VHS-0104)
    - M.G. Jones: Consumer Rights in Credit Transactions #134, Undated (Box 113, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-058)
    - Michael Pollet Legal Seminar, 2004 Dec. 15 (Box 105, Video-cassette RL11802-MDV-003)
    - Packets to: President Carter, 2004 Apr. 07 (Box 85, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-372)
    - People in Low Income Areas pay more for Goods & Services, 1993 Oct. 6-7 (Box 85, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0362)
    - Planned Confusion Consumer Series #1, Undated (Box 75, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-113)
    - Points of View Arts Funding, 1987 May 19 (Box 76, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-096)
    - Product Safety Workshop, Annual Mtg. Audio quality Poor #184a, 1973 Oct. (Box 113, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-074)
    - Product, Industry and Consumer News (microfilm), 1959-1969 (Box 138, Film-reel RL11802-F16-206)
    - Product, Industry and Consumer News (microfilm), 1959-1969 (Box 138, Film-reel RL11802-F16-207)
    - Product, Industry and Consumer News (microfilm), 1970-1975 (Box 138, Film-reel RL11802-F16-208)
    - Product, Industry and Consumer News (microfilm), 1970-1975 (Box 138, Film-reel RL11802-F16-209)
    - Radio Free America-NAB Sports #297, Undated (Box 116, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-104)
    - Rethink Afghanistan, Undated (Box 61, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-045)
    - Satellite & Cable TV, 2003 Mar. 03 (Box 102, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0995)
    - Satellite Radio, 2005 Mar. 12 (Box 108, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0871)
    - Sinclair, Carnegie, Eleanor Roosevelt, Darrow, H. Johnson, McCarthy, Rachel Carson, Coolidge & LaGuardia #241, Undated (Box 115, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-146)
    - Soul of a People: Federal Writers Project Smithsonian, Undated (Box 61, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-049)
    - Speaking for Consumer, 1970 Jan. 18 (Box 2, Film-reel RL11802-F16-016)
    - Speaking for Consumer David Schoenfeld, 1969 Feb. 16 (Box 27, Film-reel RL11802-F16-120)
    - Stereotyping in the Workplace, 1996 July 24 (Box 60, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0055)
    - Stereotyping in the Workplace, 1996 June 06 (Box 60, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0050)
    - Stereotyping in the Workplace, 1996 June 06 (Box 60, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0054)
    - Stereotyping in the Workplace, 1996 June 27 (Box 60, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0052)
    - Tape #10 Poverty Conference, 1986 (Box 35, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-035)
    - Tape #11 Poverty Conference, 1986 (Box 35, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-039)
    - Tape #12 Workshop - Minimum Wage, 1986 (Box 35, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-040)
    - Tape #13 Workshop - Food Programs, 1986 (Box 35, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-041)
    - Tape #14 Workshop - Housing, 1986 (Box 35, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-042)
    - Tape #15 Ending Poverty: Issues for the Middle Class, 1986 (Box 35, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-014)
    - Tape #16 Poverty Conference, 1986 (Box 35, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-023)
    - Tape #17 The Future, 1986 (Box 35, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-043)
    - Tape #2 Conference on Ending Poverty, 1986 Nov. 20 (Box 35, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-030)
    - Tape #3 Changing Structure of Workforce, 1986 Nov. 20 (Box 35, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-025)
    - Tape #4 Mayor Riley, Undated (Box 35, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-026)
    - Tape #4 The role of TV in our Society, 1973 Jan. 05; 1973 Jan. 06 (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-005)
    - Tape #5 Food & Hunger, Workshops, 1986 Nov. 20 (Box 35, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-018)
    - Tape #6 Ending Poverty, 1986 Nov. 20 (Box 35, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-019)
    - Tape #7 Poverty Conference, 1986 Nov. 20 (Box 35, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-020)
    - Tape #8 Opening Remarks, 1986 Nov. 21 (Box 35, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-021)
    - Tape #8 Poverty Conference Opening, 1986 Nov. 21 (Box 35, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-024)
    - Tape #9 What's Happening to the Middle Class, 1986 (Box 35, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-034)
    - Thain: Consumerism and the Regulation of Advertising #133, Undated (Box 113, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-057)
    - The Fourth Network #296c, Undated (Box 116, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-101)
    - The Thin Red Line: How the Poor Still Pay More, Undated (Box 88, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-194)
    - The Yes Men Fix the World, Undated (Box 61, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-037)
    - Working past Retirement, ???? Aug. 04 (Box 100, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0787)
- Consumer Reports Publications, 1998-2006; 2
  Primarily includes documentation and digitized elements and issues of Consumer Reports' print publications.
  - Consumer Reports, 1998-2006; 7
    - April & May 2005 Issue Disc 1 of 1 (Box 133, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-496)
    - April 1999 AR, 1999 Apr. (Box 127, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-576)
    - April 2000 Disc 1 of 1, 2000 Apr. (Box 128, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-600)
    - April 2001 Issue Disc 1 of 1 (Box 129, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-552)
    - April 2004 Issue Disc 1 of 3 (Box 132, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-465)
    - April 2004 Issue Disc 2 of 3 (Box 132, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-466)
    - April 2004 Issue Disc 3 of 3 (Box 132, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-467)
    - August 1999, 1999 Aug. (Box 127, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-582)
    - August 2000 Issue Disc 1 of 5, 2000 Aug. (Box 128, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-607)
    - August 2000 Issue Disc 2 of 5, 2000 Aug. (Box 128, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-608)
    - August 2000 Issue Disc 3 of 5, 2000 Aug. (Box 128, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-609)
    - August 2000 Issue Disc 4 of 5, 2000 Aug. (Box 128, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-610)
    - August 2000 Issue Disc 5 of 5, 2000 Aug. (Box 128, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-611)
    - August 2001 Issue Disc 1 of 3, 2001 Aug. (Box 130, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-622)
    - August 2001 Issue Disc 2 of 3, 2001 Aug. (Box 130, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-623)
    - August 2001 Issue Disc 3 of 3, 2001 Aug. (Box 130, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-624)
    - August 2002 Issue Disc 1 of 3 (Box 136, Optical-disc Rl11802-OP-417)
    - August 2002 Issue Disc 2 of 3 (Box 136, Optical-disc Rl11802-OP-418)
    - August 2002 Issue Disc 3 of 3 (Box 136, Optical-disc Rl11802-OP-419)
    - August 2003 Issue Disc 1 of 3, 2003 Aug. (Box 131, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-661)
    - August 2003 Issue Disc 2 of 3, 2003 Aug. (Box 131, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-662)
    - August 2003 Issue Disc 3 of 3, 2003 Aug. (Box 131, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-663)
    - August 2004 Issue Disc 1 of 1 (Box 133, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-478)
    - August 2005 Issue Disc 1 of 1 (Box 133, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-505)
    - August 2006 Issue (Box 134, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-512)
    - August 98 Disc II, 1998 Aug. (Box 127, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-562)
    - August 98 Toothpaste, 1998 Aug. (Box 127, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-561)
    - December 1998 Disc 1, 1998 Dec. (Box 127, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-569)
    - December 1998 Disc 2, 1998 Dec. (Box 127, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-570)
    - December 1999 Disc 1 of 2, 1999 Dec. (Box 128, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-592)
    - December 1999 Disc 2 of 2, 1999 Dec. (Box 128, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-593)
    - December 2000 Issue Disc 1 of 4 (Box 129, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-526)
    - December 2000 Issue Disc 2 of 4 (Box 129, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-527)
    - December 2000 Issue Disc 3 of 4 (Box 129, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-540)
    - December 2000 Issue Disc 4 of 4 (Box 129, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-541)
    - December 2001 Issue Disc 1 of 3, 2001 Dec. (Box 130, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-635)
    - December 2001 Issue Disc 2 of 3, 2001 Dec. (Box 130, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-636)
    - December 2001 Issue Disc 3 of 3, 2001 Dec. (Box 130, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-637)
    - December 2002 Issue Disc 1 of 4, 2002 Dec. (Box 131, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-641)
    - December 2002 Issue Disc 2 of 4, 2002 Dec. (Box 131, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-642)
    - December 2002 Issue Disc 3 of 4, 2002 Dec. (Box 131, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-643)
    - December 2002 Issue Disc 4 of 4, 2002 Dec. (Box 131, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-644)
    - December 2003 Issue Disc 1 of 3 (Box 132, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-454)
    - December 2003 Issue Disc 2 of 3 (Box 132, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-455)
    - December 2003 Issue Disc 3 of 3 (Box 132, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-456)
    - December 2004 Issue Disc 1 of 3 (Box 133, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-486)
    - December 2004 Issue Disc 2 of 3 (Box 133, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-487)
    - December 2004 Issue Disc 3 of 3 (Box 133, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-488)
    - December 2006 Issue (Box 134, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-519)
    - February 1999, 1999 Feb. (Box 127, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-573)
    - February 2000 Issue Disc 1 of 2, 2000 Feb. (Box 128, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-596)
    - February 2000 Issue Disc 2 of 2, 2000 Feb. (Box 128, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-597)
    - February 2001 Issue Disc 1 of 3 (Box 129, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-545)
    - February 2001 Issue Disc 2 of 3 (Box 129, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-546)
    - February 2001 Issue Disc 3 of 3 (Box 129, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-547)
    - February 2002 Issue Disc 1 of 4 (Box 136, Optical-disc Rl11802-OP-403)
    - February 2002 Issue Disc 2 of 4 (Box 136, Optical-disc Rl11802-OP-404)
    - February 2002 Issue Disc 3 of 4 (Box 136, Optical-disc Rl11802-OP-405)
    - February 2002 Issue Disc 4 of 4 (Box 136, Optical-disc Rl11802-OP-406)
    - February 2003 Issue Disc 1 of 2, 2003 Feb. (Box 131, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-647)
    - February 2003 Issue Disc 2 of 2, 2003 Feb. (Box 131, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-648)
    - February 2004 Issue Disc 1 of 2 (Box 132, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-460)
    - February 2004 Issue Disc 2 of 2 (Box 132, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-461)
    - February 2005 Issue Disc 1 of 2 (Box 133, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-493)
    - February 2005 Issue Disc 2 of 2 (Box 133, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-494)
    - February 2006 Issue (Box 134, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-510)
    - January 1999 Disc 1, 1999 Jan. (Box 127, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-571)
    - January 1999 Disc 2, 1999 Jan. (Box 127, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-572)
    - January 2000 Issue Disc 1 of 2, 2000 Jan. (Box 128, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-594)
    - January 2000 Issue Disc 2 of 2, 2000 Jan. (Box 128, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-595)
    - January 2001 Issue Disc 1 of 3 (Box 129, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-542)
    - January 2001 Issue Disc 2 of 3 (Box 129, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-543)
    - January 2001 Issue Disc 3 of 3 (Box 129, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-544)
    - January 2002 Issue Disc 1 of 3, 2002 Jan. (Box 130, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-638)
    - January 2002 Issue Disc 2 of 3, 2002 Jan. (Box 130, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-639)
    - January 2002 Issue Disc 3 of 3, 2002 Jan. (Box 130, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-640)
    - January 2003 Issue Disc 1 of 2, 2003 Jan. (Box 131, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-645)
    - January 2003 Issue Disc 2 of 2, 2003 Jan. (Box 131, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-646)
    - January 2004 Issue Disc 1 of 3 (Box 132, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-457)
    - January 2004 Issue Disc 2 of 3 (Box 132, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-458)
    - January 2004 Issue Disc 3 of 3 (Box 132, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-459)
    - January 2005 Issue Disc 1 of 4 (Box 133, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-489)
    - January 2005 Issue Disc 2 of 4 (Box 133, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-490)
    - January 2005 Issue Disc 3 of 4 (Box 133, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-491)
    - January 2005 Issue Disc 4 of 4 (Box 133, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-492)
    - January 2006 Issue (Box 134, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-509)
    - July 1999 Disc 1, 1999 July (Box 127, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-580)
    - July 1999 Disc 2, 1999 July (Box 127, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-581)
    - July 2000 Disc 1 of 2, 2000 July (Box 128, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-605)
    - July 2000 Disc 2 of 2, 2000 July (Box 128, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-606)
    - July 2001 Issue Disc 1 of 4, 2001 July (Box 130, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-618)
    - July 2001 Issue Disc 2 of 4, 2001 July (Box 130, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-619)
    - July 2001 Issue Disc 3 of 4, 2001 July (Box 130, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-620)
    - July 2001 Issue Disc 4 of 4, 2001 July (Box 130, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-621)
    - July 2002 Issue Disc 1 of 3 (Box 136, Optical-disc Rl11802-OP-414)
    - July 2002 Issue Disc 2 of 3 (Box 136, Optical-disc Rl11802-OP-415)
    - July 2002 Issue Disc 3 of 3 (Box 136, Optical-disc Rl11802-OP-416)
    - July 2003 Issue Disc 1 of 4, 2003 July (Box 131, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-657)
    - July 2003 Issue Disc 2 of 4, 2003 July (Box 131, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-658)
    - July 2003 Issue Disc 3 of 4, 2003 July (Box 131, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-659)
    - July 2003 Issue Disc 4 of 4, 2003 July (Box 131, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-660)
    - July 2004 Issue Disc 1 of 4 (Box 132, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-474)
    - July 2004 Issue Disc 2 of 4 (Box 132, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-475)
    - July 2004 Issue Disc 3 of 4 (Box 132, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-476)
    - July 2004 Issue Disc 4 of 4 (Box 132, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-477)
    - July 2005 Issue Disc 1 of 1 (Box 133, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-504)
    - July 2006 Issue (Box 134, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-516)
    - June 1999 Disc 1, 1999 June (Box 127, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-578)
    - June 1999 Disc 2, 1999 June (Box 127, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-579)
    - June 2000 Disc 1 of 2, 2000 June (Box 128, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-603)
    - June 2000 Disc 2 of 2, 2000 June (Box 128, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-604)
    - June 2001 Issue Disc 1 of 4, 2001 June (Box 130, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-614)
    - June 2001 Issue Disc 2 of 4, 2001 June (Box 130, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-615)
    - June 2001 Issue Disc 3 of 4, 2001 June (Box 130, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-616)
    - June 2001 Issue Disc 4 of 4, 2001 June (Box 130, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-617)
    - June 2002 Issue Disc 1 of 3 (Box 136, Optical-disc Rl11802-OP-411)
    - June 2002 Issue Disc 2 of 3 (Box 136, Optical-disc Rl11802-OP-412)
    - June 2002 Issue Disc 3 of 3 (Box 136, Optical-disc Rl11802-OP-413)
    - June 2003 Issue Disc 1 of 3, 2003 June (Box 131, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-654)
    - June 2003 Issue Disc 2 of 3, 2003 June (Box 131, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-655)
    - June 2003 Issue Disc 3 of 3, 2003 June (Box 131, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-656)
    - June 2004 Issue Disc 1 of 4 (Box 132, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-470)
    - June 2004 Issue Disc 2 of 4 (Box 132, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-471)
    - June 2004 Issue Disc 3 of 4 (Box 132, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-472)
    - June 2004 Issue Disc 4 of 4 (Box 132, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-473)
    - June 2005 Issue Disc 1 of 1 (Box 133, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-503)
    - June 2006 Issue (Box 134, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-515)
    - March & April 2006 Issue (Box 134, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-511)
    - March 1999 Disc 1 of 2, 1999 Mar. (Box 127, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-574)
    - March 1999 Disc 2 of 2, 1999 Mar. (Box 127, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-575)
    - March 2000 Disc 1 of 2, 2000 Mar. (Box 128, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-598)
    - March 2000 Disc 2 of 2, 2000 Mar. (Box 128, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-599)
    - March 2001 Issue Disc 1 of 4 (Box 129, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-548)
    - March 2001 Issue Disc 2 of 4 (Box 129, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-549)
    - March 2001 Issue Disc 3 of 4 (Box 129, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-550)
    - March 2001 Issue Disc 4 of 4 (Box 129, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-551)
    - March 2002 Issue Disc 1 of 2 (Box 136, Optical-disc Rl11802-OP-407)
    - March 2002 Issue Disc 2 of 2 (Box 136, Optical-disc Rl11802-OP-408)
    - March 2003 Issue Disc 1 of 2, 2003 Mar. (Box 131, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-649)
    - March 2003 Issue Disc 2 of 2, 2003 Mar. (Box 131, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-650)
    - March 2004 Issue Disc 1 of 3 (Box 132, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-462)
    - March 2004 Issue Disc 2 of 3 (Box 132, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-463)
    - March 2004 Issue Disc 3 of 3 (Box 132, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-464)
    - March 2005 Issue Disc 1 of 1 (Box 133, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-495)
    - May & June 2005 Issue Disc 1 of 6 (Box 133, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-497)
    - May & June 2005 Issue Disc 2 of 6 (Box 133, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-498)
    - May & June 2005 Issue Disc 3 of 6 (Box 133, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-499)
    - May & June 2005 Issue Disc 4 of 6 (Box 133, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-500)
    - May & June 2005 Issue Disc 5 of 6 (Box 133, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-501)
    - May & June 2005 Issue Disc 6 of 6 (Box 133, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-502)
    - May 1999, 1999 May (Box 127, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-577)
    - May 2000 Disc 1 of 2, 2000 May (Box 128, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-601)
    - May 2000 Disc 2 of 2, 2000 May (Box 128, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-602)
    - May 2001 Issue Disc 1 of 5 (Box 129, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-553)
    - May 2001 Issue Disc 2 of 5 (Box 129, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-554)
    - May 2001 Issue Disc 3 of 5 (Box 129, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-555)
    - May 2001 Issue Disc 4 of 5 (Box 129, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-556)
    - May 2001 Issue Disc 5 of 5 (Box 129, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-557)
    - May 2002 Issue Disc 1 of 2 (Box 136, Optical-disc Rl11802-OP-409)
    - May 2002 Issue Disc 2 of 2 (Box 136, Optical-disc Rl11802-OP-410)
    - May 2003 Issue Disc 1 of 3, 2003 May (Box 131, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-651)
    - May 2003 Issue Disc 2 of 3, 2003 May (Box 131, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-652)